{
    "id": "3d132d6dd22140baa0c705647aac1d0e",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He teaches English. / English ................... by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taught",
                "is taught",
                "was taught"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The child is eating bananas. / Bananas .................... by the child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are eaten",
                "are being eaten",
                "have been eaten"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is writing a letter. / A letter ....................... by her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is written",
                "is being written",
                "has been written"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The master punished the servant. / The servant ......................... by the master.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is punished",
                "was punished",
                "has punished"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was writing a book. / A book ....................... by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was written",
                "had written",
                "was being written"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who wrote this letter? / By whom ......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was this letter written",
                "was this letter being written",
                "had this letter written"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody cooks meal every day. / Meal ...................... by someone every day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is cooked",
                "has cooked",
                "is cooking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He wore a blue shirt. / A blue shirt .................... by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wore",
                "was wore",
                "was worn"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "May God bless you with happiness! / ................... with happiness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "May you blessed",
                "May you be blessed",
                "May blessed you be"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They are building a house. / A house ...................... by them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is built",
                "is being built",
                "was built"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have finished the job. / The job .......................... by me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has finished",
                "has been finished",
                "is finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I sent the report yesterday. / The report ................... yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is sent",
                "was sent",
                "had sent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}